Everyone's favourite bee is back!
Maya the Bee: The Golden Orb is a adventure, animation,
family film directed by Noel Cleary.
When Maya, a headstrong little bee, and her best friend Willy, rescue an ant princess, they find themselves in the middle
of an epic bug battle that will take them to strange new worlds and test their friendship to its limits.
Maya (voice), played by Coco Jack Gillies.
Willy (voice), played by Benson Jack Anthony.
Crawley / Additional voices (voice), played by Jimmy James Eaton.
Miss Cassandra / Aphids (voice), played by Tess Meyer.
Queen (voice), played by Justine Clarke.
Colonel (voice), played by Cam Ralph.
Maya the Bee: The Golden Orb (also called Maya the Bee 3: The Golden Orb) is a
2021 animated adventure comedy film directed by Noel Cleary.
Loosely based on characters from the 1975 anime Maya the Honey Bee and the German children's book The Adventures of Maya the Bee by Waldemar Bonsels, the film is a sequel to
the 2018 film Maya the Bee: The Honey Games, and stars the original voice cast of Coco Jack Gillies, Benson Jack Anthony, Frances Berry and Christian Charisiou.
The Golden Orb was originally scheduled to be released in Australia on 17 June 2020, but
due to the COVID-19 pandemic, the film was pushed back to 7 January 2021.
The film explores themes of friendship,
anthropomorphism, european, 3d animation, cartoon bee.